It's the end of one year and the start of another.
这是一年的结束，也是新一年的开始。
You've probably been considering New Year's resolutions and you may have decided to take up something new for the year ahead.
你可能一直在考虑新年计划，也许你已经决定为接下来的一年开始做一些新的事情。
Perhaps, like Debbie Gustig, you could start ballet classes.
也许，像黛比·古斯蒂格一样，你可以开始上芭蕾课。
At the age of 53, Debbie stepped into the dance studio, where, for a while, it feels like 'the outside world is on pause'.
53岁时，黛比走进舞蹈工作室，在那里，有那么一会儿，感觉"外面的世界暂停了"。
Hobbies are a way for us to keep busy and take our minds off the realities of work and life.
爱好是我们保持忙碌、让思绪从工作和生活的现实中抽离出来的一种方式。
People crave time to pursue interests that are valuable and satisfying.
人们渴望有时间去追求有价值且令人满足的兴趣爱好。
Humans have indulged in pastimes since the beginning of time, from drawing on cave walls to playing video games.
人类从远古时代就开始沉迷于消遣活动，从在洞穴墙壁上绘画到玩电子游戏。
Some hobbies involve collecting things.
有些爱好涉及收集物品。
That means acquiring, possibly cataloguing, and then displaying or storing something precious, whether that be stamps, antiques or comic books.
这意味着获取、可能进行编目，然后展示或储存一些珍贵的东西，无论是邮票、古董还是漫画书。
Linda de Ruiter turned her hobby into a job.
琳达·德鲁伊特把她的爱好变成了一份工作。
She is a yarn maker and now the owner of a small business.
她是一名纱线制作师，现在是一家小企业的老板。
After helping out a friend with a stand at a craft market, she realised she wanted a stand for herself.
在帮助朋友在工艺品市场上摆摊之后，她意识到自己想要一个属于自己的摊位。
She told the BBC she always thought yarn making would just be 'a glorified hobby' for her, but she's glad to have been proven wrong and says she is "having a ball".
她告诉BBC，她一直以为纱线制作对她来说只是一种"吹嘘的爱好"，但她很高兴自己被证明是错的，并说她"玩得很开心"。
People often pursue hobbies as a way of de-stressing.
人们常常把追求爱好作为一种减压方式。
In Canada, axe throwing is on the rise.
在加拿大，扔斧头正流行起来。
In fact, there is even an axe-throwing league with branches across the country and more than 1,500 members.
事实上，甚至有一个扔斧头联盟，在全国各地设有分支，拥有超过1500名成员。
League founder Matt Wilson told the BBC that it's "a zen sort of experience because it's really not about power, but there is definitely something cathartic about the activity".
联盟创始人马特·威尔逊告诉BBC，这是一种"禅宗般的体验，因为它真的与力量无关，但这项活动绝对有某种宣泄的效果"。
So, ballet, collecting stamps, yarn making, axe throwing?
那么，芭蕾、集邮、纱线制作、扔斧头？
What will you pursue in the new year?
新的一年你会追求什么呢？